Log in

Community

Navigation

Help and rules

Affiliates

Wiki tools

|  (last updated on _Oct 09, 2024_) |
| --- |
| Welcome, new users! To get comfortable with the community, check out our [Beginner's Guide to the Community](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Community_guide "PikminFanon:Community guide"). If you need more help, be sure to ask some of your fellow users!<br><br>If you are not signed in, please [log in](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/Special:UserLogin "Special:UserLogin") or [create an account](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/Special:CreateAccount "Special:CreateAccount") and join the community! |
| Recently, an important point was added to the beginning of the [privacy policy](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Privacy_policy "PikminFanon:Privacy policy") concerning user age. |

PikminFanon:Privacy policy
==========================

From Pikmin Fanon

*  [View source](https://pikminfanon.com/w/index.php?title=PikminFanon:Privacy_policy&action=edit "This page is protected.
    You can view its source [e]")

Page tools

 [Printable version](javascript:print(); "Printable version of this page [p]")

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|  | This page contains information relating to Pikmin Fanon's [policies and guidelines](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Policies_and_guidelines "PikminFanon:Policies and guidelines"). |  |

[Pikmin Fanon](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:About "PikminFanon:About")'s **privacy policy** details the minimum age a user must be, the nature of the data collected from users, and who may access this data. Users who do not qualify for or agree with any portion of this policy should not use Pikmin Fanon.

Users that have any questions or concerns regarding the collection and use of their data or would like to request to have their personal data removed should contact a [bureaucrat](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/Special:ListUsers/bureaucrat "Special:ListUsers/bureaucrat"), on their talk page.

Contents
--------

User age
--------

United States law prohibits anyone under 13 years old from making online accounts on any website, wikis such as Pikmin Fanon included. A user that reveals their age to be 12 or younger will be banned from the wiki until they are roughly 13 years old, to avoid legality issues.

Data
----

### Session

All content on Pikmin Fanon is open to the public for viewing and editing. Session data such as IP address, browser, operating system, screen resolution, and geographic location may be recorded by Pikmin Fanon through [cookies](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Cookie_policy "PikminFanon:Cookie policy"). This information is used to help improve the quality of the wiki's services, and will never be distributed to third parties without the approval of the relevant users.

### Personal and account

Users that register an account on Pikmin Fanon will have data such as their username, email address, and other provided details recorded in order for the wiki to identify them. Users may access and edit their data by visiting their [preferences page](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/Special:Preferences "Special:Preferences") while logged in. This data will never be shared with any third parties, and the wiki staff will endeavor to ensure that users' data is kept secure insofar as is reasonably possible.

Pikmin Fanon can not be held responsible for any personal information posted publicly on the wiki. Users should not share any more than is absolutely necessary, in accordance with the [code of conduct](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Code_of_conduct "PikminFanon:Code of conduct").

User accounts can not be deleted. When users register an account on Pikmin Fanon, they agree to all necessary data being retained indefinitely.

Contributing
------------

When users contribute to the wiki, such as by editing a page or uploading a file, the system will record their username and all content they add, change, or remove. This data is publicly accessible for anyone to view or distribute, and once a contribution is made, is released irrevocably under the terms of the [GNU Free Documentation License 1.3](https://www.gnu.org/licenses/fdl-1.3.en.html). By contributing, users agree to this data being recorded and released.

Content submitted to Pikmin Fanon is the work of its editors; as such, Pikmin Fanon's owners and staff can not be held responsible for any content that may be considered offensive, inappropriate, misleading, or which may expose private data. However, wiki staff promises to attempt to monitor all incoming contributions and to remove any such content as soon as possible.

External links
--------------

Pikmin Fanon is not responsible for the content or data collection policies of any websites users may visit through external links on the wiki. Users follow external links at follow own risk.

* * *

| --- | --- |
| Policies |     |
| Content | [General](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:General_content_policy "PikminFanon:General content policy") • [Featured content](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Featured_content "PikminFanon:Featured content") • [Deletion](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Deletion_policy "PikminFanon:Deletion policy") |
| Other policies | [Cookie](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Cookie_policy "PikminFanon:Cookie policy") • [Ethics](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Code_of_conduct "PikminFanon:Code of conduct") • [Poll](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Poll_policy "PikminFanon:Poll policy") • Privacy • [Talk page](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Talk_page_policy "PikminFanon:Talk page policy") |
| Guidelines |     |
| Content | [General](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:General_content_guidelines "PikminFanon:General content guidelines") • [Files](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:File_guidelines "PikminFanon:File guidelines") • [Content list](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Content_list_guidelines "PikminFanon:Content list guidelines") • [Disambiguations](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Disambiguation_page_guidelines "PikminFanon:Disambiguation page guidelines") |
| Specific articles | [Areas](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Area_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Area article guidelines") • [Caves](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Cave_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Cave article guidelines") • [Stages](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Stage_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Stage article guidelines") • [Characters and ships](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Character_and_ship_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Character and ship article guidelines") • [Collectibles](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Collectible_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Collectible article guidelines") • [Enemies and vegetation](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Enemy_and_plant_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Enemy and plant article guidelines") • [Families](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Family_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Family article guidelines") • [Games](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Game_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Game article guidelines") • [Pikmin](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Pikmin_article_guidelines "PikminFanon:Pikmin article guidelines") |
| Templates | [General](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Template_guidelines "PikminFanon:Template guidelines") • [Navigation box](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/PikminFanon:Navigation_box_guidelines "PikminFanon:Navigation box guidelines") |

Retrieved from "[https://pikminfanon.com/w/index.php?title=PikminFanon:Privacy\_policy&oldid=185667](https://pikminfanon.com/w/index.php?title=PikminFanon:Privacy_policy&oldid=185667)"

[Categories](https://pikminfanon.com/wiki/Special:Categories "Special:Categories"):

* This page was last edited on 12 June 2024, at 13:37.
* Content is available under [Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/) unless otherwise noted.
